[
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 5, 34, 41, 43, 44?",
    "correctAnswer": "41",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "40",
      "41",
      "42"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 8, 9, 14?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 7, 9, 26, 42, 45?",
    "correctAnswer": "26",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "25",
      "26",
      "27"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 2, 11, 15, 21, 33?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "14",
      "15",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 15, 39, 49?",
    "correctAnswer": "39",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "38",
      "39",
      "40"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 13, 18, 33, 34, 41?",
    "correctAnswer": "33",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "32",
      "33",
      "34"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 7, 13, 21, 24, 46?",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "21",
      "22",
      "23"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 6, 14, 19, 35, 38?",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "19",
      "20",
      "25"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 2, 10, 12, 24, 31?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the median <br> of 9, 11, 12, 13, 23?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "12",
      "13",
      "17"
    ]
  }
]